A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller gubernatorial records, Office Subject Files, Second Administration, Series 37.2 FA439A
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Second Administration, 1963-1966; 2; 120 microform reels
  - Public Works (Reel 91, Reel 92, Reel 93, Reel 94)
    - Highways (Reel 92, Reel 93, Reel 94)
      - Local Roads (Reel 93, Frame 65)
      - Nassau Expressway (Reel 93, Frame 78)
      - Long Island Bridge (Reel 93, Frame 96)
      - Verazanno Narrows Bridge (Reel 93, Frame 118)
      - Nassau Expressway (Reel 93, Frame 126)
      - Newburgh-Beacon Bridge (Reel 93, Frame 129)
      - Niagara Thruway (Reel 93, Frame 131)
      - Route 9 (Reel 93, Frame 140)
      - Route 9A (Reel 93, Frame 144)
      - the Northway (Reel 93, Frame 149)
      - Route 117 (Reel 93, Frame 156)
      - Prospect Mountain Parkway (Reel 93, Frame 164)
      - Richmond Parkway (Reel 93, Frame 170)
      - Saw Mill River Parkway (Reel 93, Frame 213)
      - Southern Tier Expressway (Reel 93, Frame 217)
      - Route 17 (Reel 93, Frame 229)
      - Sheridan Expressway (Reel 93, Frame 263)
      - Route 28 (Reel 94, Frame 2)
      - Thruway (Reel 94, Frame 19)
      - Westchester Parkways (Reel 94)
      - A-Z (Reel 94, Frame 25)
      - General (Reel 94, Frame 132)
    - Topics (Reel 94)
      - Billboards (Reel 94, Frame 170)
      - Federal Highway Program (Reel 94, Frame 179)
      - Grade Crossing Elimination (Reel 94, Frame 187)
      - Snow Removal (Reel 94, Frame 195)
      - Tree Removal (Reel 94, Frame 195)
      - Signs (Reel 94, Frame 200)
  - Resignations & Vacancies (Reel 94, Reel 95)
    - County (Reel 94, Frame 214)
    - State (Reel 94, Reel 95)
      - Authorities & Commissions (Reel 94, Frame 224)
      - Conservation (Reel 94, Frame 231)
      - Department of Correction (Reel 94, Frame 238)
      - Education Department (Reel 94, Frame 240)
      - Executive Department (Reel 95, Frame 2)
      - Health Department (Reel 95, Frame 11)
      - Labor (Reel 95, Frame 13)
      - Mental Hygiene (Reel 95, Frame 19)
      - Welfare (Reel 95, Frame 32)
      - State University (Reel 95, Frame 39)
      - Agriculture (Reel 95, Frame 55)
      - Judiciary Courts (Reel 95, Frame 67)
      - General (Reel 95, Frame 73)
  - Veterans (Reel 95)
    - Korean Bonus (Reel 95, Frame 85)
    - General (Reel 95, Frame 102)
    - Division of Veterns Affairs (Reel 95)
      - Letters of Commendation (Reel 95, Frame 113)
    - Division of Veterns Affairs (Reel 95, Frame 121)
    - Institutions (Reel 95, Frame 130)
    - Division of Veterns Affairs (Reel 95, Frame 131)
  - Welfare (Reel 95, Reel 96)
    - Department of (Reel 95)
      - Board of Social Welfare (Reel 95, Frame 138)
      - Commission for the Blind (Reel 95, Frame 141)
      - Indian Affairs (Reel 95, Frame 148)
      - Institutions (Reel 95, Frame 159)
      - General (Reel 95, Frame 180)
    - General (Reel 95, Reel 96)
      - Assistance Cases (Reel 95, Frame 201)
      - Day Care (Reel 95, Frame 219)
      - Welfare Costs (Reel 95, Frame 222)
      - Moreland Commission (Reel 95)
        - 1963 February-December (Reel 95, Frame 228)
        - 1963 January-February (Reel 96, Frame 3)
      - General (Reel 96, Frame 20)
  - Youth (Reel 96, Reel 97)
    - General (Reel 96, Reel 97)
      - Young American Medal (Reel 96, Frame 148)
      - Division of (Reel 96, Frame 158)
      - Governor's Conference on Children & Youth
        - 1963 February-1964 June (Reel 96, Frame 222)
        - 1963 January (Reel 97, Frame 7)
      - Juvenile Delinquency (Reel 97, Frame 8)
      - Local Youth Centers (Reel 97, Frame 21)
      - Sale of Liquor to Minors (Reel 97, Frame 21)
      - School Dropouts (Reel 97, Frame 65)
      - Youth Camps (Reel 97, Frame 72)
      - Youth Corps (Reel 97, Frame 82)
      - Council on Youth (Reel 97, Frame 98)
      - General (Reel 97, Frame 107)
  - Organizations
    - A Study of American States - Amalgamated Silver Workers Union (Reel 97, Frame 182)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science - American Retirement Foundation, Inc. (Reel 98)
    - American Right of Way Association - Board of Higher Education (1966) (Reel 99)
    - Board of Higher Education (1963-1966 January) - West Genesee Junion Chamber of Commerce (Reel 100)
    - Challenge 67 - Council on Foreign Relations (1965 May-1966). (Reel 101)
    - Council on Foreign Relations (1963-1965 May) - Federated Garden Club of New York State (1963-1966). (Reel 102)
    - Federated Garden Club of New York State (1963) - Governor's Conference Committee on Civil Defense and Post-Attack Recovery (1965 May-1966) (Reel 103)
    - Governor's Conference Committee on Civil Defense and Post-Attack Recovery (1963-1965 February) - International Association of Governmental Labor Officials (1964-1966) (Reel 104)
    - International Association of Governmental Labor Officials (1963) - Livingston County Volunteer Fireman's Association (Reel 105)
    - Lobsenz Public Relations Company - National Conference of Christians and Jews (Reel 106)
    - National Conference on Community Health Services - New York Typographical Union (1963-1966) (Reel 107)
    - New York Typographical Union (1966) - New York State Teachers Association (Reel 108)
    - New York State Title Association - Radio-Newsreel-Television and Working Press Association (1966 March) (Reel 109)
    - Radio-Newsreel-Television and Working Press Association (1963-1965) - The Schenectady Opera Guild (Reel 110)
    - The Schenectady Patrolmen's Benevolent Association - Urban Renewal Association (Reel 111)
    - Underwear Institute - Zoological Society of Buffalo (Reel 112)
  - Supplemental material (Reel 120)
    - Miscellaneous Supplemental Files (Reel 120)
    - Administration - Public Works (Reel 120)
    - Index (Reel 120)